const qBank = [
  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["Kilo, kilo"],
    questionId: "1",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["FAL, fal"],
    questionId: "2",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["M4, m4, ,M4A1, m4a1"],
    questionId: "3",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["FR 5.56, FAMAS, fr 5.56, famas"],
    questionId: "4",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["Oden, oden"],
    questionId: "5",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["M13, m13"],
    questionId: "6",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["Scar, scar"],
    questionId: "7",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["AK-47, ak-47, ak, AK"],
    questionId: "8",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["RAM, ram"],
    questionId: "9",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["Grau , grau 5.56, GRAU, Grau 5.56, grau"],
    questionId: "10",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["AMAX, amax, CR-56 AMAX, cr-56 amax"],
    questionId: "11",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["AN-94, an-94, AN, an"],
    questionId: "12",
  },

  {
    question: "What gun is this?",
    answer: ["AS VAL, VAL, val, as val"],
    questionId: "13",
  },
];

export default qBank;
